EMILE DURHAM

Santa Rosa, CA | +17079789600 | durhamemile@gmail.com | emiledurham.com

Professional Summary

A tech enthusiast interested in pursuing a career that interprets data meaningfully. Motivated to learn, grow and excel in web development and data analysis. Background in health, business and technology. Lived and worked across three different continents. Fluent in English, French and Portuguese (BR).

Technical skills

- Python
- Django/Flask
- Postgres/MySQL

- Pandas/Numpy
- HTML/CSS/Bootstrap
- Git/Github

Work History

Data InternBikeep OÜ

Jun 2020 - Sep 2020
Tallinn, Estonia

- UX/UI design creating interactive dashboards using Dash
- Data cleaning and basic analysis with MySQL and Python
- Geospatial data analytics of bike parking locations

Management Assistant

Triumf Health

Oct 2019 - Dec 2019 Tallinn, Estonia

Involved with product development and UI testing of mobile therapeutic game

- Contacting potential clients and stakeholder follow-up
- Created and updated physical records and digital files to maintain current, accurate and compliant documentation
- Responsible for updating translated documents, databases and website to reflect modern English usage

Marketing/Business Consulting Intern

Jan 2017 - May 2017 Healdsburg, California

InHouse Creative + Sales

• Gathered, documented and modeled data to assess business trends

- Compiled research data and gave professional presentations highlighting finds and recommended optimizations
- Resolved customer problems, improved operations and provided exceptional client support

Education

Bootcamp: Full-Stack Python

09/2020

Software Development Academy 311 hours

Tallinn, Estonia

Master of Science: Health Food Innovation Management

Maastricht University

01/2019 Venlo, NL

Bachelor of Arts: International Studies

12/2016

University of Oregon

Eugene, OR